Previously on the show. Wolffy worked with the goats to catch his duplicates.
Trong tập trước, Sói Xám cùng các bạn Cừu đi bắt bản sao của hắn.
However, things kept going wrong at crucial moments.
Nhưng mọi thứ lại tệ đi.
After many defeats, the goats and the wolf
Thất bại nên Sói Xám và Cừu
played cat and mouse with the duplicates and finally forced them to give in.
chơi trốn tìm với bản sao để bắt chúng.
Suddenly, a duplicate dropped into a waterspout
Bỗng một bản sao rơi
as a result of a series of coincidences.
vào vòi rồng vì không may.
What is going on?
Cuối cùng là có chuyện gì vậy?
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: The Underwater Conspiracy"
"ĐẢO BAY: THÁM HIỂM BẦU TRỜI: ÂM MƯU DƯỚI NƯỚC"
I can't become one again if one is missing.
Nếu thiếu một thì không thể hợp lại.
What should we do?
Làm gì đây?
Wolffy, let's go down to save that duplicate.
Sói Xám. Đi cứu bản sao đó thôi.
Sure.
Tất nhiên.
It's rare to see Wolffy so enthusiastic.
Hiếm khi Sói Xám nhiệt tình.
I don't want to be like this for the rest of my life!
Ta không muốn như này cả đời.
Come on, let's go down the waterspout in Magic Train.
Đi thôi, dùng tàu Ma thuật đi.
You're not driving Sirius?
Thế còn Thiên Lang?
A waterspout is so dangerous.
Lốc xoáy nguy hiểm lắm.
What if my precious Sirius gets damaged?
Nếu Thiên Lang của ta bị hỏng thì sao?
Magic Train...
Tàu Ma Thuật...
Weslie, this is the oxygen spray.
Cừu Vui Vẻ, đây là xịt ô xy.
Spray it on your body and you can breathe under water.
Xịt lên là thở được dưới nước.
It's very chaotic inside a waterspout. Contact us if anything happens.
Trong vòi rồng rất hỗn loạn. Gọi ta nếu có vấn đề nhé.
Okay. Let's go!
Vâng ạ. Đi thôi!
My plan worked!
Kế hoạch thành công!
We came to save you!
Bọn ta đến đây!
One, two...
Một, hai...
three…
ba...
Come on, give me your hand.
Đưa tay ra đây.
I've finally grouped all my duplicates.
Cuối cùng đã đủ phân thân.
Now we shall combine!
Giờ thì hợp nhất thôi!
Wonderful! I'm back to normal now.
Tuyệt! Giờ ta trở lại như thường rồi.
Weslie!
Cừu Vui Vẻ!
Hold on tight!
Giữ chặt vào!
Thank goodness you and the sky crystal are both all right.
May là ngươi và viên đá không sao.
Weslie...
Cừu Vui Vẻ...
You don't have to thank me.
Không phải cảm ơn.
No, I want to say--
Không, ta muốn nói...
Really, you don't have to thank me.
Thật mà, khỏi cảm ơn.
No, I just wanted to ask, if you're here, who is controlling Magic Train?
Không, ta chỉ muốn hỏi là ai đang điều khiển tàu Ma Thuật?
Let's fix Magic Train as soon as we can.
Đi sửa tàu ngay thôi.
Luckily, we didn't drive Sirius down here.
May không phải Thiên Lang.
Weslie, are you all right?
Cừu Vui Vẻ, con ổn chứ?
We're fine, but Magic Train is broken.
Ôn ạ, nhưng tàu Ma Thuật hỏng .
What about the sky crystal?
Thế viên đá bầu trời?
The sky crystal is with me.
Nó đây ạ.
The sky crystal doesn't work underwater.
Viên đá có hoạt động dưới nước đâu.
Hurry back up after you've fixed Magic Train.
Mau quay trở lại khi sửa xong nhé.
Stay safe!
Bảo trọng!
With me, Wolffy, around, he is absolutely safe.
Có Sói Xám ta ở đây thì khỏi lo.
It's not safe because you're around!
Có ngươi nên mới nguy hiểm đó.
Is it an earthquake?
Động đất ư?
-Magic Train! -Don't worry about it. Run over there!
- Tàu Ma Thuật! - Kệ đi. Qua đây!
Weslie is in danger! We have to go save him.
Cừu Vui Vẻ gặp nguy! Ta phải cứu cậu ấy.
But we don't have Magic Train. How can we get down there?
Nhưng không có tàu Ma Thuật mà?
Let's go find Sirius.
Thế tìm Thiên Lang đi.
Luckily, we ran away quickly.
May mà chạy kịp.
Is anyone here...
Có ai không...
Is someone trapped by the fallen rocks?
Có ai kẹt dưới đống đá kìa?
Come on, let's go in and take a look.
Đi vào trong xem sao.
Magic Train is damaged!
Tàu Ma Thuật bị hỏng rồi!
Are Weslie and Wolffy all right?
Cừu Vui Vẻ và Sói Xám sao rồi?
Weslie!
Cừu Vui Vẻ!
Weslie, where are you?
Cừu Vui Vẻ, cậu ở đâu?
Wolffy! Weslie and Wolffy aren't in here.
Sói Xám! Họ không ở đây.
Wolffy...
Sói Xám...
Mom, has Dad gone missing?
Mẹ, ba mất tích rồi ạ?
No. Dad is just playing hide-and-seek with us.
Không. Ba đang chơi trốn tìm với mình thôi.
Then I can surely find Dad.
Thế con sẽ đi tìm ba.
They should be around here.
Họ chắc ở quanh đây thôi.
Then we'll go and find them.
Cùng đi tìm họ thôi.
Chief, please stay here and wait for news.
Trưởng Làng ở đây chờ tin nhé.
Okay, I'll stay behind to fix Magic Train just in case.
Được, ta sẽ ở đây sửa tàu Ma thuật.
We'll go and find them too.
Ta cũng đi.
It's too dangerous underwater. You two should stay here.
Dưới nước quá nguy hiểm. Hai người ở đây.
Yes. We can't afford to lose Willie while we're trying to find Wolffy.
Đúng vậy. Không thể để lạc Sói Con khi đi tìm Sói Xám được.
All right.
Được rồi.
They're not here.
Họ không ở đây.
They're not here either.
Cũng không ở đây.
I've searched over there, but can't find them either.
Tớ tìm bên kia cũng không.
Weslie!
Cừu Vui Vẻ!
I'm here!
Tớ ở đây!
It's Weslie's voice!
Giọng Cừu Vui Vẻ!
It seems to have come from the cave.
Hình như là từ cái hang.
Weslie!
Cừu Vui Vẻ!
I'm here!
Ở đây!
Weslie's here!
Cậu đây rồi.
You came!
Cậu đã đến!
Why are you trapped?
Sao cậu lại kẹt thế?
We'll save you!
Bọn tớ tới đây!
Weslie, are you all right?
Cừu Vui Vẻ có sao không?
I'm fine.
Tớ ổn.
There are traps here. Be careful, everyone.
Có bẫy ở đây. Cẩn thận nhé.
Then let's get out of here immediately.
Vậy ra khỏi đây đi.
Stay close and don't lose anyone.
Ở gần nhau và đừng lạc nhé.
Can't you see such a handsome wolf here?
Ngươi không thấy Sói đẹp trai ta sao?
I forgot Wolffy is here too.
Tớ quên Sói Xám cũng ở đó.
You're not that bad after all.
Cũng không tệ lắm.
Wolnie and Willie came too. Let's get out of here quickly.
Sói Đỏ và Sói Con cũng đến đó. Đi thôi.
Willie, Dad's coming!
Sói con, ba đến đây!
Wolffy, you're running too fast.
Sói Xám chạy nhanh quá.
Can't you see such a cute fish here?
Các ngươi không thấy ta ư?
Oh, right, there's a little fish too.
Ờ phải, có một bạn cá ở đây nữa.
Right, why were you trapped here?
Đúng rồi, sao các cậu lại bị kẹt?
Weslie and I heard a voice, so we went into the cave.
Cừu Vui Vẻ và tớ nghe có tiếng nên vào xem.
We found this little fish trapped inside.
Bọn tớ thấy bạn cá bị kẹt.
I went to save him because I'm kind and ended up trapped with Weslie.
Ta đến cứu hắn vì lòng tốt và cuối cùng cũng bị kẹt luôn.
I went into the cave to hide from the falling rocks,
Tớ trốn vào hang để tránh đá,
then a dark shadow passed behind me,
thì bỗng một bóng đen lướt qua,
and I was caught in a trap.
rồi tớ bị kẹt luôn.
A dark shadow?
Một bóng đen?
I'm finally done fixing Magic Train.
Đã sửa xong tàu Ma Thuật.
Mommy, I see Dad.
Mẹ ơi, con nhìn thấy ba.
This must be the data recorder of Magic Train.
Đây hẳn là dữ liệu được ghi lại của tàu.
Hold on.
Chờ đã.
Did he cause the rocks to fall?
Hắn đã làm đổ các tảng đá ư?
Village Chief.
Trưởng Làng.
Children, glad to know you're all right.
Mấy đứa không sao là tốt rồi.
Weslie, you have to be careful!
Cừu Vui Vẻ hãy cẩn thận!
That fish might be a villain.
Con cá đó có thể là kẻ xấu.
Weslie...
Cừu Vui Vẻ...
Weslie! Little fish, what are you doing?
Cừu Vui Vẻ! Cá nhỏ, cậu làm gì vậy?
Little fish?
Cá nhỏ?
Who told you I'm a fish?
Ai bảo ngươi ta là cá?
Oh, no, I'm stuck... Give me a little time.
Ôi bị kẹt rồi... Chờ ta chút.
This is...
Đây là...
A black cloud person?
Người mây đen?
I've been lying low among you for a long time.
Ta đã trốn ở dưới các ngươi lâu rồi.
The video camera on Magic Train,
Máy quay ở tàu Ma Thuật,
the note picked up by Mechanical Bird, I did all that.
Chim Máy nhặt được tờ giấy đều do ta làm.
In order to get the sky crystal,
Để lấy được viên đá bầu trời,
I even lured you to go underwater.
ta còn lừa các ngươi xuống nước.
But I didn't expect you to escape from the falling rocks.
Nhưng không ngờ ngươi lại thoát được đá rơi.
I see. You pretended to be trapped and lured us into the cave.
Rồi ngươi giả bị bẫy dụ bọn ta vào hang.
No. Actually, I wanted to lure you into the cave.
Không, ta đã muốn dụ các ngươi vào hang.
When you came close to me, I would press the red button and trap you.
Khi ngươi đến gần thì ta sẽ bấm nút đỏ bẫy ngươi.
But there's dirt on such a perfect remote control!
Nhưng có vết bẩn ở trên điều khiển!
I can't let that happen.
Không được.
I pressed the wrong button!
Ta đã ấn nhầm nút!
So I modified my plan and continued to lure you.
Vì vậy ta thay đổi một chút để dụ ngươi.
I'm here!
Tớ ở đây!
Someone's trapped. We'll save you.
Ai đó bị kẹt kìa. Mau ra cứu.
I intended to trap you after you saved me.
Ta định gài bẫy sau khi ngươi ra cứu.
However, I left a thread on the remote control when I wiped it.
Nhưng lại có một sợi lông ở điều khiển.
We're trapped too.
Tớ bị kẹt rồi.
That is how we all ended up being trapped.
Đó là sao chúng ta đều bị kẹt.
It doesn't matter anymore because I've got the sky crystal!
Dù sao thì cuối cùng ta cũng có được viên đá rồi!
-What do you need the sky crystal for? -I'm going to destroy it.
- Ngươi cần nó làm gì? - Ta sẽ phá hủy nó.
That is my gem. I won't let you destroy it.
Viên ngọc của ta sao có thể để ngươi hủy.
Give it back to me.
Trả lại đây.
Let's help Wolffy.
Ta cũng tới.
I caught him.
Bắt được rồi.
Really?
Thật không?
You can't escape. Give in now.
Đừng hòng chạy. Đưa đây.
I won't give in easily.
Ta không bỏ cuộc dễ thế đâu.
Goodbye, everyone!
Tạm biệt nhé!
Don't go!
Đứng lại!
Children...
Các cháu...
Are you all right?
Ổn cả chứ?
Village Chief, the sky crystal was taken. Let's hurry and get it back.
Trưởng Làng, viên đá bị lấy mất rồi. Mau đi lấy lại.
Wolnie, Willie, this place is too dangerous. Let's get out of here.
Sói Đỏ, Sói Con, nơi này quá nguy hiểm. Mau ra khỏi đây.
Wolffy, aren't you going to help us chase the villain?
Sói Xám, ngươi có đi cùng không?
I don't get myself involved in dangerous things like that.
Ta không muốn đi mấy chuyện nguy hiểm.
I'm taking my wife and son away from this dangerous place.
Ta sẽ đưa vợ con đi càng xa càng tốt.
In that case, we'll chase the villain ourselves.
Nếu thế thì bọn ta sẽ tự đi vậy.
Okay.
Được.
TO BE CONTINUED
CÒN TIẾP